Guide to the Stanford University, Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, Records SC0705
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2004-166
  - Nancy Barnett: Women in Athletics Spring 1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Our Children Fall 1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Publicity: Fall 1985 Lectures (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Childcare Panel--Fall 1985 "Children in Daycare" (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Registration: Women in the Teen Years--Fall 1985 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Women in the Teen Years: Program Development, Committee, Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Gallery of Women (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Rethinking Rape (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Publicity for "Women in Religion" Winter 1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Dorm Program: Catholic Women (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Program Planning/ "Women in Religion" Winter 1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence / "Women in Religion" Winter 1986 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Arrangements: Spring 1986, "The Writer: A Passion for Her World" (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Publicity: Spring 1986, "The Writer: A Passion for Her World" (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Autobiography and Biography: Gender, Text, and Context--April 11-13, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Publicity--Fall 1986 Lyman Lecture (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Program Development/Fall 1986 "Psychology of Women" (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Bram Dijkstra--Fall 1986 "Psychology of Women: Theory/Therapy" (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Sherri Matteo--Fall 1986 "Psychology of Women" (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - TERESA LAFROMBOSIE (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Nancy Chodorow--Fall 1986 "Psychology of Women: Theory/Therapy" (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Deborah Rose--Fall 1986 "Psychology of Women: Theory/Therapy" (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Atkinson, Jane--Conference on Theo. Perspectives (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Chodorow, Nancy--Conf: Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Collier, Jane--Conf: Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Deaux, Kay--Conf: Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Degler, Carl--Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Dupre, John- Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Friedman, Lawrence- Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Gagnier, Regina- Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Hooks, Bell (Gloria Watkins)--Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Hubbard, Ruth--Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Jaggar, Alison- Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Kay, Herman Hill- Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Maccoby, Eleanor- Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - MacKinnon, Catharine- Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Middlebrook, Diane--Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Noddings, Nel--Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Proposal: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference (Conference) (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Funding- Conf: Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - General Correspondence--Conf: Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff.Participants (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Draft Requests--Conf: Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Poster and Flier--Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Addendum--Conference on Theoretical Perspectives (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Gender Articles (for Deborah Rhode's Editing) (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Publicity, Mailings, Etc.--Conf. on Theor. Persp. Sex. Diff. (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Winter 1987 Lyman Noon Lectures: Ruth Doell, Helen Longino, Deborah Rhode (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - News Releases--Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Poster- Lyman Spring ' 87 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Alice Kahn--Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Funding--Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Dance Brigade- Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Female Troubles- Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Facilities & Technical Services--Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Ladies Against Women--Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Regenia Gagnier--Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Marga Gomez--Lyman Spring '87 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Jing Lyman Lectures Spring 1987--"Women's Humor and Satire" (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Fall 1987 International Feminism (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Fall 1987 Contact Letter (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - JLL: Flyers and Posters, 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - The Lyman Lectures 87-88 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - JLL: Publicity, 1987-88" (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Project Diversity (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Jing Lyman Fall 1987--International Feminism: Third World Women (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Fall '87--Poster--International Feminism (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Fall '87--CVs (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Fall '87--Corazon Aquino (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Fall '87--Sonia Alvarez (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Fall '87--F. Nilufer Cagatay (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Fall '87--Lioba Moshi (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Fall 1987 -Cynthia Enloe (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Fall '87--Christine Obbo (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Fall '87--Adrienne Rich (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Fall '87--Ana Perla (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Fall '87--Raquel R. Sancho (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Fall '87--Haunani-Kay Trask (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Fall '87--Sylvia Wynte (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Poster "Love and Sex" Lyman Lecture Winter '88 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Winter '88 Reception--Katchadourian (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Winter '88 Publicity--"Love and Sex" (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Winter '88 Tomas Almaguer (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Workshop--Sylvia Cerel Bowen '88 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Workshop--Eileen Eya '88 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Workshop Sean Reynolds (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Winter '88 Estelle Freedman (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Winter '88 Herant Katchadourian (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Winter '88 Annette Lawson (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Winter '88 Nancy Shaw (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Winter '88 Debbie Then (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Spring '88 Lyman Lecture (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Spring '88 Poster--Lyman Lecture "Women Making Music" (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Spring '88 Publicity: Lyman Lecture (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Spring '88 "Blazing Redheads" (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Spring '88 Holly Near (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Spring '88 Tamara Brooks (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Spring '88 Dimensions of Difference Performance (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Spring '88 Judy Fjell (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Spring '88 Panel (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Spring '88 Penny Rosenwasser (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Spring '88 Ginny Berson (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Spring '88 Carmen Vasquez (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Spring '88 Mary Watkins (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Spring '88 Constitutional Celebrations--Women and Law Day--Unfinished Agenda (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Law Day Poster 4-28-88 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 4/28 Catharine MacKinnon (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 4/28 Christine Curtis (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 4/28 Angela Glover Blackwell (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 4/28 Mary C. Dunlap (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Visitors '87-'88 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Oct. 87 German Marshal Fellows (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 0/20 Institute Open House (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 1/12/87 You Can Make a Difference Conference (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - 2/4 Pat Williams--morning coffee talk (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - IRWG Flyer 4/28/88 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - 4/29/88 Models of Maternal Care (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - October 2, 1988 Betty Friedan (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Oct. 26, 88 Why Men Are The Way They Are (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Oct. 1988 Women of the Americas (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - April 14, 1989 Gloria Steinem (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Ugandan Refugee Exhibit Feb/Mar 1989 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - May 8, 1989 Ecological Feminism--Bag lunch w/ Prof Irene Diamond (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - May 11, 1989--Organ Music By Women Composers--Christa Rakich (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Thursday-05-18, 1989 "Our Changing Population: Where Headed" (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Feminist Theory Seminar 1988-89 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Jing Lyman Retrospective--Alysanne McGaffey Dec 88--Feb 89 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - April 1989 Lee Lawson Exhibit (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Africa Unadorned--Reception, Talks Summer 1988" (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Africa Unadorned--General Info. Summer 1988 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Africa Unadorned--Publicity '88 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Africa Unadorned--Correspondence '88 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Swedish Visitors 1988 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Oct. 26, 1988 Swedish--Presenters (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Oct. 26, 1988 Swedish--Publicity (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Oct. 26, 1988 Swedish--Poster (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Oct. 26, 1988 Swedish--Bag Lunch, etc. (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Nov. 4, 5 1988--Divorce Conference--Proposal (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Nov. 4, 5 1988--Divorce Conference--General" (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - (Lyman Lecture Fall '88: Health Across the Life Span)--General Topic Information (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Fall 1988 Publicity: Health Across the Life Span (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Fall 1988 Laura Carstensen (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Fall 1988 Jose B. Cuellar (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Fall 1988 Barbara Ehrenreich (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Fall 1988 C. Barr Taylor (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Assemblywoman K. Jacqueline Speier (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Fall 1988 Schedule--Health Fair '88 Taking Action (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Fall '88 Binders for Conference Attendees--Health Fair: Taking Action (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Fall 1988 Deirdre English (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Fall 1988 Nathan Maccoby (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Fall 1988 Robert Marcus (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Fall 1988 Kay Woodruff (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Fall 1988 Linda Clever (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Fall 1988 Fredi Kronenberg (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Fall 1988 Sadja Greenwood (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Fall 1988 Julian Davidson (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Fall 1988 Linda Giudice (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Fall 1988 Marcia Stefanick (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Fall 1988 Kevyn Allard (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Fall 1988 W.A.R.M. (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Fall 88--United Way Health Fair Info. (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Winter 1989 Publicity (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Winter 1989 Schedule (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Winter 1989 Surrogacy Panel (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Winter 1989 Hilary Hanafin (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Winter 1989 Miriam Johnson (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Winter 1989 Donna Hitchens (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Winter 1989 Michael Lamb (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Winter 1989 Robert Mnookin (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Kathleen McConnell Winter 1989 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Winter 1989 Julien S. Murphy (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Winter 1989 Nancy Reame (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Winter 1989 Pat Williams (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Winter 1989 Alberta Siegel (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Spring 1989 Publicity (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Spring 1989 Rachel Bagby (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Spring 1989 Jean Bolen (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Spring 1989 Marilyn Fabe (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Spring 1989 Margaret Mackenzie (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Spring 1989 BAWP Publicity (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - May 6, 1989 BAWP. People for Accessible Health Care" (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Spring 1989 BAWP--Program/Invitation (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Lee Lawson Exhibit (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Barbara Mendelsohn Exhibit (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - GAIA Women's Health Lecture Series Winter 1990 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Fall '89 JL Schedule (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Fall '89 Jing Lyman--Publicity (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Fall '89 Jing Lyman--Annette Lawson (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Fall '89 Jing Lyman--Claire Brindis (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Fall '89 Jing Lyman- Sandy Dornbusch (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Fall '89 Jing Lyman- Edward Zigler (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Fall '89 Jing Lyman--Marlene Cole (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Fall '89 Jing Lyman--Kate Walton (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Fall '89 Jing Lyman--Myra Strober--Mommy Track Panel (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Winter JL 1990 General (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Winter JL 1990 Publicity (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Winter JL ' 90 Anna Kuhn (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Winter JL '90 Madeline Kahn (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Winter JL '90 Marilyn Yalom (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Winter JL '90 Jean-Marie Apostolides (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Winter JL '90 Whitney Chadwick (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Winter JL '90 Arturo Islas (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Winter JL '90 Jane Collier (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Winter JL '90 Gertrude Lehnert-Rodiek (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Winter JL '90 Sandra L. Bem (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Winter JL '90 Janice Ross (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Spring 1990 Jing Lyman General (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Spring JL 1990 Publicity (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Spring JL 1990 Goldman Publicity (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Spring JL 1990 Margo Horn (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Spring JL 1990 Laura Flax (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - JLL: Fall 1990 International Perspective on Maternal and Child Health (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Campus Reports and Stanford Dailys- Copies w/ articles about JLLS Fall 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1990 Jing Lyman--Betsy Hartmann (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fall 1990 Jing Lyman--Neera Sohoni (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fall 1990 Jing Lyman--Sylvia Ceral (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fall 1990 Jing Lyman--Ruth Greenblatt (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fall 1990 Jing Lyman--Ward Cates (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fall 1990 JL Series--Donald Francis (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fall 1990 Jing Lyman--Robert Hatcher (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fall 1990 Jing Lyman--Soheir Morsy (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fall 1990 Jing Lyman--Ruth Sidel (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Winter 1991 Jing Lyman Publicity (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Winter 1991 Jing Lyman Lectures--Edith Gelles (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Winter 1991 JLL--Benjamin A. Saenz (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Winter 1991 JLL--William Youngs (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Winter 1991 JLL--Marilyn Yalom & Susan Groag Bell (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Winter 1991 JLL--Barbara Babcock (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Winter 1991 JLL--Diane Middlebrook (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Winter 1991 JLL--Gloria Hull (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991 Publicity (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991- Helen Leong, 4/10/91 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991-Lisa Stelck 4/10/91 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991--Rachel Bagby 4/24/91 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991--Roxanne Nilan 5/1/91 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991--Jing Lyman 5/8/91 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991--Cecilia Burciaga 5/15/91 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991--Herant Katchadourian (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series Spring 1991--Linda Hawes Clever 5/29/91 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Planning Materials (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Publicity (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Linda Giudice 10/16/91 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Carl Djerassi 10/23/91 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Diana Pearce 10/30/91 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Michael Wald 11/06/91 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Debra Satz 11/3/91 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Diana Akiyama 11/20/91 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Fall 1991 Jing Lyman--Ashley Phillips 12/04/91 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Winter 1992 Jing Lyman Publicity (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Winter 1992 Jing Lyman--Pedro Noguera 1/22/92 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Winter 1992 Jing Lyman--Kathy Jones 1/29/92 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Winter 1992 Jing Lyman--Toni Tomacci 2/5/92 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Winter 1992 Jing Lyman--Bernadine Fong 2/12/92 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Winter 1992 Jing Lyman--Deborah Rhode 2/19/92 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Winter 1992 Jing Lyman--Aileen Hernandez 3/4/92 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Spring 1992 JLL--Publicity (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Spring 1992 JLL--Nancy Adler 4/22/92 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Spring 1992 JLL--Yvonne Maldonado 4/29/92 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Spring 1992 JLL--Madeleine Kahn 5/6/92 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Spring 1992 JLL--Diana Dutton 5/13/92 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Spring 1992 JLL--Iris Litt 5/20/92 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Past Lyman Flyers (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Annette Lu--Taiwanese Feminist (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Book Party Flyers (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Catalog of Lyman Lecture Tapes (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Equal Rights Advocates (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - FACTS SHEETS (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Feminist Studies Program Committee (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Institute 92-93 Natl. Advisory Panel (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Institute News (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - IRWG Corporate Lists (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Institute Scholars Addresses 10/92 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Institute Tax Exempt Documents (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Office for Multicultural Development (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Past Institute Events (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Potential Speakers Information (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Yokohama Forum (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - JLL Fall 92 Institute Scholars Intros. (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - JLL Fall 92 Publicity (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - JLL Fall 92 Budget (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - JLL Fall 92 Lyman Marketing Letter (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - JLL Fall 92 Potential Donors List (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - JLL Fall 92 Authorization Forms--KPFA completed (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - JLL Fall 92 Authorization Forms--completed (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - JLL Fall 92 Alice Bach (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - JLL Fall 92 Bulbul (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - JLL Fall 92 Student Panel (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - JLL Fall 92 Jean Fetter (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - JLL Fall 92 Thomas Arnold (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - JLL Fall 92 Nicole Johnson (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - JLL Fall 92 Mae Lee (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - JLL Fall 92 Monisha Pasupathi (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - JLL Fall 92 Carol Sanger (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - JLL Fall 92 Barrie Thorne/Marilyn Yalom (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - JLL Fall 92 Andrew Lisac (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - JLL Fall 92 Michael Kimmel (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - JLL Fall 92 Janet Halley (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - JLL Winter 93 Authorization Forms (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - JLL Winter 93 Funding (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - JLL Winter 93 Budget (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture tape orders Winter 93 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - JLL Winter 93 Linda Lomperis (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - JLL Winter 93 Edith Gelles (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - JLL Winter 93 Shulamit Magnus (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - JLL Winter 93 Yung-Hee Kwon (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - JLL Winter 93 Barbara Christian (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - JLL Winter 93 Francesca Miller (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - JLL Winter 93 Karen Offen (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - JLL Spring 93 Speaker Forms (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - JLL Spring 93 Wanda Corn (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - JLL Spring 93 Sherri Matteo (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - JLL Spring 93 Jan Krawitz (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - JLL Spring 93 Judith Brown (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - JLL Spring 93 Will Roscoe (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - JLL Spring 93 Rachel Cohon (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - JLL Spring 93 Szonja Szelenyi (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Fall 1993 Jing Lyman Lectures (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - JLL Fall 93 Susan Groag Bell (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - JLL Fall 93 Elisabeth Hansot (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - JLL Fall 93 Ellen Peal (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - JLL Fall 93 Mark Hall-Patton (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - JLL Fall 93 Christa Johnson (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - JLL Fall 93 Betje B. Klier (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - JLL Fall 93 Sally Gearhart (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Winter 1994 Lyman Series (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Fundraising (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Panel: Castle, Roscoe, Reinhold, Katz (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Wilfrid Koponen (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Paul Robinson (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Morris Kaplan (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Karl Knapper (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Estelle Freedman (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Sharon Holland (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Erin Carlston (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Jared Braiterman (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - JLL Winter 1994 Linda Garber (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Spring Quarter Lyman Series 1994 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - JLL Spring 1994 Karen Offen April 6, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - JLL Spring 1994 Kate Karpilow April 13, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - JLL Spring 1994 Glenna Mathews April 20, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - JLL Spring 1994 Judy Bloom April 27, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - JLL Spring 1994 Neera Sohoni-05-11, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - JLL Spring 1994 Kathy Jones-05-25, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - JLL Spring 1994 Congresswoman Anna Eshoo (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Jing Lyman Lecture Series as of 10/94 Miscellaneous lectures & seminars (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Linda's Files
    - CROW lecture series 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Publicity--Across JLL Series (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Jing Lyman Lecture Series 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Lyman Lectures 2003/2004 – 11/5/03 Sheppard (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Lyman Lectures 2003/2004 – 10/8/03 Matson (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Jing Lyman Lectures 2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Patricia Karlia-Newmann (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Deborah Rhode (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Joel Beinin (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Yvonne Yarbro-Bejarano (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Diann McCants (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Yoshiko Matsumoto (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Purnima Mankekar (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Denise Lynn Johnson, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Jing Lyman Lecture Series 2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Dennis Carter (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Robert Friedland (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Gwendolynne Yeo (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Mary Goldstein (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Elizabeth Roden (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Lyman Lectures – Old files (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Hazel R. Markus 1/21/98 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Jing Lyman Lectures: listings and articles 1997-98 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 1998 Evaluations (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 1998 Lyman Fundraising (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Johnetta Cole Reception 11/6/98 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Deborah Rhode 11/5/97 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Cynthia Fuchs Epstein 3/4/98 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Tara VaDerveer 5/20/98 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - JLL: Angela LeBlanc 4/22/98 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Frank Furstenburg 2/98 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Eleanor Maccoby LLS 1998-99 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Langendorf LLS 1998-99 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Felstiner LLS 1998-99 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Cowan 5/12/99 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Banks 1998-99 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Botcheva 1998-99 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Hackman 1998-99 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Gotlib (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Design Group (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Brochure: Creative Touch Design 2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Creative Touch Design (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Bio Laura Carstensen (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - CV Laura Carstensen (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Articles (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Women's Health Research Luncheon 1/7/98 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Women's Health Research Seminar winter 1997 publicity (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - WHRS and Lyman flyers--old (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Gianturco/Tuttle (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Robert Butler, lunch/talk (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Betty Friedan (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2004-215
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Director's search files restricted 75 years from date of creation.
  - Associates Board Files
    - Institute Committees 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Institute Committees l993-94 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Institute Committees 1992-93 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Institute Committees 1991-prior (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 15th Anniversary Celebration, March 9, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Associates Board Correspondence 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Board Minutes 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Associates Board 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Associates Board Minutes 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Associates Board Correspondence 1998-99 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Associates Board Correspondence 1997-98 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Associates Board Correspondence 1996-97 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Board Correspondence 1995-96 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Board Correspondence 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Board Minutes 1998-99 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Associates Evening Thursday,-02-20, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)